(Leonard:)Well, what if we go
around the university
(Leonard:)and just get
the patent ourselves?
(Leonard:)We can't.
It says on their Web site,
(Howard:)as long as we work there,
they have
(Howard:)a controlling ownership
of anything we come up with.
(Sheldon:)Great, so they own
my idea for a T-shirt
(Sheldon:)that says
“Dumb as a Bag of Geologists.”
(Leonard:)Well, our choices are we
do this with the university
(Leonard:)or we don't do it at all.
(Howard:)Either way, I get nothing.
(Leonard:)Or, if we ended up
making money from this,
(Leonard:)Sheldon and I could split
our shares with you.
(Sheldon:)To be clear,
(Sheldon:)Leonard is referring
to the gyroscope,
(Sheldon:)not the T-shirt and mugs.
Oh! Now they own the mugs.
(Howard:)I guess that is
a way around this.
(Howard:)You guys would be cool
doing it like that?
(Leonard:)Of course, we can split
any profits three ways.
(Sheldon:)I'm fine with that.
(Howard:)Okay, great.
(Sheldon:)It sounds like a, uh,
contract might be in order.
(Leonard:)Sure, we could write
something up.